Hello friends, hello, so
friends, today we are going to tell you
how we insure two-wheelers, four-wheelers, and large vehicles through the CSC portal. So,
before giving information about this, I would like to
tell you about our YouTube channel.
If you
get good information from our YouTube channel, then
you should like, subscribe,
and share it with your friends. So
friends, let's go to the CSC portal.
This is the test board of our CSC portal. From
here we will
give you complete information about how to insure a vehicle. As you log in to the
CSC portal,
interest will come in this way. Here you will search for
HDFC
[Music]
company, from where you
can search and insure. Friends, you can do it from here.
Friends, you have to search here [
Music]. When a
new page opens, its dashboard will look like this.
Friends, here you can see that it is
for motor,
here it is two-wheeler, and here it is DP
third party, it is for tax. In this way,
different options have been given for all of them.  Friends,
if you want to do two wheeler
then you will click on two wheeler here, like if we
click here then if we want to do
first party then by clicking here
if we want to do
third party then by clicking here
we will immediately put it as first party
[Music]
after entering the number you have to search here,
like click on get retail, the
complete details of the vehicle will be displayed. The
most speciality of this portal is that like
we enter the bike number of our vehicle
then its complete details are displayed,
from where did you get it, from which manufacturing
startup it is, which company it belongs to, all this
rest is not there friends, so you
can do it like this and if you can see then the
showroom price of the vehicle in this way,
friends,
if you want to make the full value then
keep it complete here and you can do it individually here
[Music]
so it is
shown here how much it is, how much is it doing,
you can do your first party insurance for 1500
friends and after that you will do it again, in
this way the complete details of the vehicle have been displayed
and here you have to enter your engine number
friends
We will enter our engine number, friends,
after entering the engine number, we will go down
and you
can nominate here, along with this, we will
enter our details below, who is the owner of the vehicle
and as per the RC book of the vehicle, so
here we fill our details,
friends, like we will enter Mr., here we will enter the
name, date of birth and here we will
enter its attachment which is base in the Aadhar card,
here we will enter the city etc. state,
so after showing you this,
you will click and your proposal will be generated
and here you will be able to see it
here, it will be done like this,
friends, here you can see
how much premium is being deducted and
you can see it here
and as soon as you
click here, it will go to your CSC portal and
from there you can deduct the payment,
so let's see this way,
friends, by doing this
we will show you, friends, there will be money,
see here I do not have balance,
it does not go further, as soon as you click, you will
enter your CSC password and after confirming the password,
your payment will be confirmed and you  In this
way, you can insure your two wheeler or four wheeler,
friends, in this
way you
can insure any bike. If
you liked our information, then like our channel,
subscribe and
share it with your friends so that you can avail the
benefit of insurance in this way.
Thank you friends.